<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Neha Satapathy</title>
    <link>http://nehasatapathy.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Neha Satapathy</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 21:59:56 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://nehasatapathy.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Navigating Ambiguity</title>
      <link>http://nehasatapathy.com/blog/navigating-ambiguity/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 21:59:56 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://nehasatapathy.com/blog/navigating-ambiguity/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I had my first existential crisis at the age of 20.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Leading up to it, I had gone through a lot of loss and changes in my life, ranging from moving to NYC for a summer to losing a close friend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I saw it coming, so I felt like I had more time to prepare&amp;hellip; but honestly, nothing really prepares you for the depressing void that opens up a few months after you graduate and start thinking about what you&amp;rsquo;re &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; doing. COVID and quarantine has probably exacerbated this for my class of 2020 folks, but it seems to be a surpringly common issue that people silently go through.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What do you do with yourself after graduating college and leaving a life of structure??&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many people choose to continue their life of structure, either by pursuing more education in grad school or by blindly climbing the corporate ladder, working towards each promotion. While I don&amp;rsquo;t find these options to be bad options necessarily, I think its important to make the distinction of &lt;em&gt;why&lt;/em&gt; you do what you&amp;rsquo;re doing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My answer to navigating the ambiguity that lurks in the shadows of any new grad is actually more spiritual and big picture than I initially realized.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One particular event in my life that I want to dive into today was my first corporate experience: my first ever Software Engineering internship! Having jumped up and down&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;was I started to ask myself questions I took for granted growing up. Questions about death, the meaning of life, and what the hell I was doing Having the nagging feeling to constantly be productive, I had plenty of free time at the start of quarantine to panic about how I should make the most of my time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In some cases, reality &lt;em&gt;does&lt;/em&gt; meet our expectations, but we soon realize that we don&amp;rsquo;t want what we thought we wanted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So what do you do when you graduate from a structured life in school and are now left?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At first thought, being in control of your life sounds daunting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Having the nagging feeling to constantly be productive, I had plenty of free time at the start of quarantine to panic about how I should make the most of my time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In some cases, reality &lt;em&gt;does&lt;/em&gt; meet our expectations, but we soon realize that we don&amp;rsquo;t want what we thought we wanted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So what do you do when you graduate from a structured life in school and are now left?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At first thought, being in control of your life sounds daunting.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Recruit At GHC</title>
      <link>http://nehasatapathy.com/blog/grace-hopper-recruiting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 19:00:30 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://nehasatapathy.com/blog/grace-hopper-recruiting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I went to my first GHC in my &lt;strong&gt;third&lt;/strong&gt; year of college.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello!</title>
      <link>http://nehasatapathy.com/blog/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 16:11:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://nehasatapathy.com/blog/hello/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- ![Alt Text](https://media.giphy.com/media/vFKqnCdLPNOKc/giphy.gif)
 --&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;welcome-to-my-first-blog&#34;&gt;WELCOME to my first blog!!!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;HELLO! My name is Neha and I have no business starting this blog &lt;em&gt;but&lt;/em&gt; I set a goal for myself to feel more comfortable writing this year and want to use this platform to document the random things I deep dive and learn about.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;a-little-bit-about-me&#34;&gt;A little bit about me..&lt;/h4&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>